Cristopher Urena

Bronx, NY 10474 curena7@fordham.edu 929-238-3105 WWW: https://criswebsite.netlify.app/

experienced in helping users correct problems with computer systems, mobile devices, and peripheral equipment. Knowledgeable about usability and computer languages. Comfortable working alone to successfully investigate and troubleshoot problems. Able to create coding projects to improve users experience.

Skills

- User Support
- Hardware Diagnostics
- Customer Service
- Application Support
- Technical Troubleshooting
- Computational Design
- Python, HTML, CSS, C++,
- Payment Collection

Work History

IT Help Desk Technician

Fordham University, Bronx, NY

September 2023 - Current

- Answered user inquiries to resolve computer software or hardware operation problems.
- Collaborated with technical staff to establish goals and objectives for system improvements and upgrades.
- Demonstrated advanced product knowledge to solve customer issues.
- Troubleshot hardware issues and worked with service providers to facilitate repairs for end users.

Administrative Assistant

Voces Speech Clinic, The Bronx, NY

April 2024 - October 2024

- provided administrative support to the executive team, including scheduling meetings and managing calendars.
- Organized and maintained filing systems for physical and electronic documents, ensuring accuracy and managing calendars.
- Greeted visitors in a professional manner, responding to inquiries and directing them to appropriate personnel.

Intern

Summer Youth Employment Program, Bronx, NY

July 2023 - August 2023

- Helped plan special events such as field trips, picnics, and BBQs.
- Supervised groups of children during recreational activities.
- Facilitated team-building exercises among different age groups of campers.
- Monitored for signs of physical and emotional distress and stopped activities to administer care when appropriate.
- Helped participants enjoy activities while ensuring adherence to protocol.

Coding Fellowship

KKCF At The Knowledge House, New York, NY

June 2022 - August 2022

- Developed web applications using HTML, CCS, JavaScript and JQuery.
- Collaborated with other developers on coding projects.
- Integrated third-party APIs into existing websites and applications.

Education

High School Diploma June 2023 AECI 2 Charter HS at The Bronx, NY

- Honoree of Cristopher U
- 3.8 GPA
- Elected to President for AECI 2's Student Governments in 2020-2022

Affiliations

- Gym
- Basketball
- Baseball
- Coding

Accomplishments

CSTEP Student at Fordham University

Certifications

• Computer languages such as JavaScript, C++, HTML